UNITE Ron Blackwell Collection of Country Files 6000/031
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Ron Blackwell Collection of Country Files
1988-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
Blackwell, Ron
6000/031
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes files of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union.
5758027
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 02, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections:
Blackwell, Ron; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
5758027
- Bangladesh - Honduras (Box 1)
  - Bangladesh (BIGWU), 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bangladesh (BIGWU), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Burma, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chile, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - China, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Costa Rica, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dominican Republic, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dominican Republic Re: Bibong Apparel Company, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dominican Republic Re: Bonahan, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dominican Republic Re: GSP, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dominican Republic: Re: Caribbean Basin Organizing, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dominican Republic Re: Levi-Strauss & Co., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - El Salvador, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fenastras, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - France, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - FITITVC 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - FITITVC 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AIFLD, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Guatemala, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Guatemala Re: Glep, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Guatemala Re: Phillips- Van Heusen (PVH), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Haiti, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Honduras, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Honduras Re: ILGWU/ACTWU Solidarity, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Honduras - Mexico (Box 2)
  - Honduras Re: National Labor Committee, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Honduras Re: NLC/Honduras Work, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Honduras: Re: Seolim, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hondurs Re: Sinitra Costura, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Honduras Re: Warnaco, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ICEF 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ILERF 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Indonesia, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ITGLWF: Strategic Approaches 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ITGLWF 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ITGLWF 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ITGLWF 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Japan, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mexico Oct. 14, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mexico 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ICFTU/ORIT 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mexico Re: ACTWU Plants, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mexico Re: AIFLD, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mexico Re: Convention Nacional Democratica (CND), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mexico Re: Democracia, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mexico Re: Ezun, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mexico Re: Fat, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mexico Re: Peso Crisis, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mexico Re: Pri, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mexico Re: Salant, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mexico Re: Sony Corp., 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mexico Re: UE/Fat, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mexico Re: Parras, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Mexico - NLC (Box 3)
  - Chronology of the Mexican Economic Crisis: Documents June 29, 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Report on the Mexican Economic Crisis, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Investment Promotion Ads, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - National Labor Committee 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - National Labor Committee 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - National Labor Committee 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NLC: Local Tour 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NLC: Mandarin Plant for the Gap Re: Women's Rights 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Reading Materials Re: Sweatshops (NLC), 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Statement of the Honorable Robert E. Rubin July 14, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Workers Rights and Trade: Democracy's Next Frontier, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)